Saebyeol Pak

Front-end developer

Profile

Detail-oriented front-end developer, friendly team player and self-motivated person. +3 years experience in building websites and web applications with a multitude of clients. Love collaboration and continually work on improving my skills.

Technical Skills

- Have work experience in implementing responsive, cross-browser web projects.
- Tested and debugged code.
- Good understanding of UX design and translation of wireframes.

SKILLS HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / JavaScript / React.js / React Hooks / GraphQL / jQuery

TOOLS Visual Studio Code / Git / Android Studio / Xcode /

OTHER UI framework / Trello / MS office

Project Experience

Easy Realty System / Front-end Developer

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

Property management system for professional real estate agents.

- Built the front-end of Easy Realty System's property lists and fetched API using React.js,
 React Hooks and Material-UI.
- Styled components with SASS.
- Tested all features.

May 2020 - Aug 2020

Kovan / Front-end Developer

All-in-one group management solution with 7 plug-ins

- Collaborated with other students to plan, executed a native app.
- Built and implemented to-do list and poll plug-in with React Native and React Hooks.
- Created graphs for poll plug-in with SVG.
- Styled the app with Native-Base.
- Built the promotional website using React.js.

Personal Project Experience

Movie App

Web app that lets you search for movies and TV shows

- Created search, filter features using React.js.
- Fetched TMDB Movie API.
- Styled the components using Material-UI.

Work Experience

Emeye (Korea) / UI developer

Dec 2015 - Dec 2017

- Built websites and web apps using HTML5, CSS3 and jQuery.
- Tested the websites and applications for usability and fixed bugs.
- Worked on websites maintenance including correcting issues and making updates.

Konest (Korea) / UI developer

Mar 2014 - May 2015

- Changed website code from HTML3 to HTML5 / CSS3 and made it responsive.
- Built web pages and updated the website.
- Customized landing pages.

Education

Langara college

May 2019 - Dec 2020

Post-Degree Diploma, Web and Mobile App Design and Development / Developer stream